Like Diane just mentioned,
就像 Diane 提到的
there are four broad categories of summary metrics.
有四大类总指标
First, there are sums and counts.
首先是 合计和计数
An example of this type of metric might be the number of users
这类指标的一个示例是
who visited some page.
访问某个网页的用户数量
Second, there are means, medians and percentiles.
第二类是平均值、中位数和百分比
For example, the mean age of all users who have completed a certain course or
例如 完成某门课程的平均年龄或
the median latency of a page load.
网页加载的中位数延迟
Third, there are probabilities and rates.
第三类是点击概率和点击率
Like you saw, a probability has 0 or 1 possible outcome in each case.
正如你看到的 在各种情况中一个概率可能是 0 或 1
For example, did the user click zero times, or one time?
例如 用户点击了 0 次 还是 1 次？
Whereas the rate could have zero or more, for
点击率可能是 0 或更多
example, the user clicks two times or four times.
例如 用户点击了两次或四次
Fourth, there are ratios.
第四类是比例
These are more general than rates, which are two counts divided by each other.
它们比点击率更普遍 两次计数彼此相除
A ratio is any two numbers divided by each other.
一个比例是一个数除以另一个数
So it could have any value.
因此 可能是任何值
Business metrics often make sense as ratios.
业务指标通常是比例
For example, you might want to measure the probability
例如 你可能想要测量
that a user clicks a link that generates revenue,
用户点击链接生成收益的概率
versus the probability that a user clicks any link on the page.
与用户点击网页上任何链接的概率
Now, let's focus in on the second category and see how we can choose
现在 我们看看第二类指标
between these different options by looking at the distribution of our data.
看如何通过查看数据的分布来选择不同的方案
To do that, let's look at an example of some simulated user data
为此 我们来看一个示例
about how long users spend on a particular page of the Audacity site.
关于用户在 Audacity 网站的某个页面花多长时间的仿真用户数据
Here, I've shown a histogram of the time spent on the page
这里 我展示一个在这个页面所花时间的直方图
where each bar is the frequency.
每个条柱都表示频率
So out of 10,000 data points,
因此 在 10,000 个数据点中
a little less than 3,000 fall in this first bucket.
第一个条柱为 3,000 以下一点
The mean of this data is about 1.3.
这个数据的平均值是 1.3 左右
That is, the average user spends about 1.3 seconds on this page.
也就是说 用户平均花 1.3 秒的时间在这个页面上
The median, on the other hand, is about 0.9.
另一方面 中位数是 0.9
That means 50% of all users spend less than a second on the page.
也就是说所有用户的一半花在这个页面上的平均值小于 1 秒
The reason for this difference is all these points off to the right.
出现这个差异的原因是所有这些点趋向右侧
They increase the mean proportional to their size, so if one user stays for
其大小的平均值成比例增加 因此 如果一个用户停留
say six seconds, then that outweighs a few users who don't stay long at all.
6 秒钟 比不停留太长时间的一些用户更有意义
This is an example of an exponential distribution.
这是一个指数分布的例子
If you're thinking about something like,
如果你想知道
how many users really get information from this page,
有多少用户真正从这个页面得到了信息
you might want to use something besides the median or the mean.
除了中位数或平均值外 你可能还想要其他指标
Maybe the 75th percentile or the 90th percentile.
也许 75% 或 90%
In addition to these possible metrics, you could take this one step further.
除这些可能的指标外 你还可以再迈进一步
Let's say you find out, in some UER studies that it would take the average
比如说 你会发现在一些用户体验研究中
person at least three seconds to read most of the content on the page.
会花费人们至少三秒钟的时间阅读页面上的大部分内容
Based on this, you could use as your metric the percent of users who spend at
因此 你可以将花费至少三秒钟时间的用户百分比
least three seconds.
用作你的指标
In this case, that would be about 11% of the data points that stay about three
在这里 约 11% 的数据点
seconds or longer.
在页面上停留三秒钟或更长时间
This metric does have its own problems, though.
虽然这个指标也有其自身的问题
What if you make the page really confusing?
如果这个页面真的让人感觉困惑会怎样？
That could artificially inflate this metric.
这会人工增大这个指标